Guide to the Theodore H. Geballe Papers SC0357
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Theodore H. Geballe papers
1970-1997
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Geballe, Theodore H.
SC0357
28.25 Linear Feet
Professional correspondence; materials from meetings, conferences, workshops, and symposia; and abstracts, notes, and transparencies from talks relating to his teaching and research in materials science, superconductivity, and electronics.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Gift of Theodore H. Geballe, 1989-2016.
Information about Access
Partially restricted; letters of recommendation and student files not open to researchers.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Professor of Applied Physics and Materials Science Engineering at Stanford University.
Description of the Collection
Professional correspondence; materials from meetings, conferences, workshops, and symposia; and abstracts, notes, and transparencies from talks relating to his teaching and research in materials science, superconductivity, and electronics.
Superconductivity.; Physics.; Geballe, Theodore H.; Stanford University. Department of Applied Physics. Faculty; Geballe, Theodore H.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1994-124
  - Panel on Outdoor Art (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Affiliates Program (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Midwest Superconductivity Consortium [Miscon] - May, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Council of Scientists and Engineers for Clinton-Gore (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Superconducting Super Collider Project [1] (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Superconducting Super Collider Project [2] (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1993 Selection Committee for the Comstock Prize (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Theoretical Physics (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1992 American Physical Society Nominating Committee (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Matthias Prize: Prof. Michael Tinkham (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Matthias Prize: Douglas J. Scalapino (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Matthias Prize: Brian Maple and Shoji Tanaka (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Matthias Prize: K.K. Likharev (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Matthias Prize: N.-P. Ong (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Matthias Prize: K. Kitazawa (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Matthias Prize: V. L. Ginzburg (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Matthias Prize: Bertram Battlog and Robert J. Cava (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Matthias Prize: Philip W. Anderson (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Matthias Prize: P. B. Allen (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Matthias Prize: Y. Tokura (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences; member (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - American Association for Advancement of Science [Chair, Section B] (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - American Institute of Physics Trigg Committee [Encyclopedia of Applied Physics] (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - External Advisory Committee Materials Research Laboratory, University of Texas Austin (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Materials Research Laboratory [MRL] External Advisory Committee (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - American Physical Society Journal Exchange (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Advisory Board, Israel. Second International Conference (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Encyclopedia of Applied Physics [Advisory Board] (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - IBM Colloquium; Dec. 18, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Department of Energy [DOE] Council on Materials; Germantown, Dec. 20-21, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bellcore, December 17, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Berkeley, April 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Materials Research Society, Fall Meeting; Boston, Nov. 26 - Dec. 1, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Ginzton Faculty Meeting, Oct. 31, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - University Orals: Mark Lee; Oct. 31, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - CMR Thrust - Oct. 1990; Open House, Site Visitors (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Air Force Superconductivity Technical Action Group [STAG] Meeting, University of Minnesota, Oct. 16, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - AT&T Reception, Meyer-Buck House; Oct. 16, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Journal Club; Oct. 10, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Takashi Suzuki visit, Oct. 8, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Applied Superconductivity Conference, Snowmass Village, Colorado, Sept. 1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - NATO Science Forum 1990; Biarritz, France; Sept. 16-21, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - NATO Advanced Study Institute; Sept. 10-20, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency [DARPA] MRC; Workshop on Superconductivity, LaJolla, July 18-19, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Geneva, Switzerland; June 27-29, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Gordon Conference, New Hampshire, June 11-15, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco, Physical Phenomena in Granular Materials, April 16-20, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Jury Duty, April 1 - June 30, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Advances in Material Science and Applications of High Temperature Superconductors [AMSAHTS], Greenbelt, MD, April 2-6,1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - OBES Materials Sciences Information Meeting; March 22, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - SPIE Advances in Semiconductors and Superconductors; San Diego, March 17-21, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Riverside Colloquium, Feb. 8, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - American Physical Society [APS] Meeting, Anaheim; March 12-16, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science [AAAS] Annual Meeting, New Orleans, Feb. 15-20, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Thin Film Materials for Information Storage, Workshop, Stanford University, Feb. 2, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - National Academy of Sciences [NAS] Committee on Energy and Transportation (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Materials and Mechanisms of Superconductivity and High-Temperature Superconductors [M2S/HTSC-III], Kanazawa, Japan; July 22-26, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - EPRI (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - International Symposium on; Tokyo, Japan (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Toshiba International; Kyoto, Japan; July 15-20, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Prof. Yurii Shevakin (Lee Miller), June 19, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 5th Joint Magnetism and Magnetic Materials (MMM)-Intermag Conference; Pennsylvania, June 18-21, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Meeting Luncheon, June 13, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Luncheon with Prof. Arakawa, June 11, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Meeting, Faculty Club; June 4, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Materials Research society [MRS] Spring Meeting, Anaheim, April 27 - May 4, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Washington, April 28 - May 1, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - William L. McLean Symposium, Rutgers University; April 26, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Kenji Yamamoto, April 25-28, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Department Oral Exam: Thierry Delmarcelle, April 18, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Italy Superconducting Conference, Rome, April 14-18, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - LBL/Berkeley/Stanford Dinner, Faculty Club, April 9, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Frank DiSalvo, April 5, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Ginzton Laboratory Visiting Committee, April 4-5, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - American Physical Society March Meeting, Ohio, March 18-22, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Ginzton Laboratory Faculty Meeting, March 11, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Journal Club, March 6, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Gordon Conference Frontiers of Science, Ventura, CA; Feb. 25 - March 1, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science [AAAS] Section Meetings, Feb. 14-19, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Diamond Films Workshop, Stanford; Feb. 1, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - National Academy of Sciences [NAS] Regional Roundtable, University of California, San Francisco, January 31, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Chao Tang, January 22 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Aspen Winter Conference, Jan. 13-20, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - EPRI Review (Bravman), Jan. 11, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - STANCOM Meeting, Jan. 10. 1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - J. Geerk, Nov. 7, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Prof. Ossipyan, Dec. 29, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Los Alamos Dec. 13, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Y. Bando, Dec. 8, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Visitors 1988-89 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Prof. Yusheng He, March 1989 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Rudy Peierls, March 14-16, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Kenji Yamamoto, Sept. 16 1988 - June 1989 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Peter Dickin, May 25, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - King-Ning Tu, Visits, May 9, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Eunice Bond Visit, May 3, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Harold Weinstock, Visits, April 27-28, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Visitors 1988 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - USSR Visitors, December 1987 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Donglu Shi (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Togano Visit, Dec. 11, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Prof. Bruce Jue, March 14-17, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Alex Mueller, Linus Pauling Lecture, Feb. 17-19, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Braginski, A. I. (Personnel) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Braginski, A. I., BRA 1.000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Borides - SmB6 (Experimental) BOR 1.000 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Amorphous Films: Properties (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - MacVicar, M. L. A., MAC 2.000 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - McMillan, W., MCM 1.000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - McSkimin, H., MCS 1.000 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Mattes, B. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Masers, MAS 1.000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Hellman, F. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - He3Rig, HE3 1.000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Supercurrents, The Superconductive Magazine [Theodore H. Geballe] November 1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1999-138
  - AFOSR PROPOSAL “Thin Film Routes to New Material” Sleight/Geballe (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AF4960-93-1-0038 - AIR FORCE Workshop: The Road to Room Temperature Superconductivity (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AFOSR - 91-0145 High Temperature Superconducting Films and Crystals - 1991 - 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AF-0081-“Fabrication and Analysis of Josephson Junction and Arrays” 9-1-90 to 8-31-93 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - White Paper on Thermionic Cooling; Kenny Pfafman, THG, Moyzhes (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - White Paper - Thermoelectric Materials; KGB, Shelton and Pickett (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ARPA - Magnetic Materials and Devices (not funded) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Proposal and White Paper 4/94, Advanced Superconducting Materials and Device Concepts by KGB and Hammond. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CMR-IRG (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - CMR - Reports (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CMR - Budget (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - STAB Instruments (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - AF - 017 (1997-2000) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - AF Proposal 11/1/97-10/31/00 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - AF 0039 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Air Force 4 Correspondences (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Air Force 4 Fiscal (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ASSERT Reports (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - AFSOR GRANT F49620-92-J-0341, FY 91 - Superconductivity of Fullerenes and Scanning Tunneling... (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - AASERT PROPOSAL SUBMITTED TO AFOSR “Boundary Effects in High-Tc Superconducting Devices, A Kapitulnik, THG (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - ASSERT Proposal (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Air Force 4 Reports (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - AFOSR-91-0145 REPORTS ’93 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - FINAL TECHNICAL REPORT, AF4 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AFOSR-91-0145, Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - AFOSR Contract F49620-92-C-0004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ginzton Labs (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Solid State Affiliates (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Board, Stanford Humanities Center, Sept. 98-2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Unrestricted Funds, Geballe (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - EPRI (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ONR-0445-Thermionics (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ONR-445, 1st Tech Report (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - AF-0373 (AASERT) 2WMA453, Progress Report 7/31/95 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Department Memos (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Applied Physics/Physics Colloq. Comm (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - AP Degree Requirements (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Academic Advisors and Advisees (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Applied Physics Colloquia (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - AF4: Technical Report, Jan.1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - AF4: Correspondences (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - AFOSR Program (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - AF4: Contract (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Proposal/Budget to AF, 9/91; Creation of a Center for Research in Superconductivity and Superconducting (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - AF1: Contract (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - AF1: Correspondences (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - EPRI Review of Jan. 11, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Stanford - Bravana, EPRI (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - EPRI Proposal (July 1988), “Fundamental Studies of Critical…” 10/4/88 - 12/31/92 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Controlled Coherence Length and Anisotropy High TC Oxides - Geballe/Beasley, submitted to BSF, 12/92 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - AFOSR Grant 1990 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - AF2: Contract (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - AF2: Final Tech Report, 6/91 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - AF2: Budget (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - AF2: Correspondences (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - AFSOR/F49620-88-K-0002, Final Report of inventions and subcontr. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Technical Report (AF2), August 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - NFS Proposal - “Synthesis, Characterization, etc.” Geballe/Shen (1991) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - SRI Final Tech. Report, CMR-R-90-4, SPO #6202, 8/90 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Lawrence Berkeley Labs (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - LBL Contract 4560210 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hewlett-Packard Collaboration (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - HP Research Agreements (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Xerox Research Agreements (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Final Report - PO B055980, CMR/Lawrence Livermore National Lab. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Richards Bolometer (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Bardeen and Matthias Prize Committee, Geballe--Chair (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - December 16-17, 1991- Germantown Council on Material Science. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - TCSUH Visit - October 11, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Conference on Supercond. And Applications, Sept. 24-26, 91; Buffalo, NY (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Jubilee Nobel Sym. Dec. 4-7, 1991; Gothenburg, Sweden (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Fall MRS, Dec.2-6, 1991; Boston, Mass. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Overheads and Graphs (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 1992 Conference (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Varian Physics Dept. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1992 Aspen Conference (summer) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Physics Review Board - U.C. Santa Cruz, May 28-29, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - April 27 - May 1, 1992; MRS, San Francisco (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - April 17, 1992 - Naval Postgraduate; School, Monterey, CA (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - American Chemical Society; April 5-10, 1992; San Francisco (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - April 2, 1992 - Lynbrook High School; San Jose, CA (Career Day) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Beijing Intl. Conference on High TC Superconductivity - May 1992 (China) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - March 1992 APS Meeting, March 16-20, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Nobel ‘92 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Gordon Conference - Jan. 6-10, 1992; Oxnard, CA (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - ACS - 1992 - August, Chicago (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Abstracts - 1991-92, 1993-94 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - CMR Presentation 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Materials Research Society 1993 Fall Meeting - November 29 - December 3 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - August 11-14, 1993 - ISEC 93; Boulder, Colorado (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Low Temperature (LT 20) - August 1993; Eugene, Oregon 4/11 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - July 27-31, 1993 - Eugene, Oregon; Molecular and Oxide Superconducters (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - NATO ARW - July 11-15, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Cast Review Panel - May 7, 1993; Washington, DC (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Annual Meeting - April 25-27, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - February 17, 1993 - University of Minnesota (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - March 22-26, 1993 APS Meeting; Seattle, Washington (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - INCOR PROJECT - Review Panel For High Temperature - Los Alamos, NM; March 4, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - February 22, 1993, NAS Roundtable; San Francisco, CA (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Class Membership Committee; Feb. 6, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Doe Workshop; August 10-14, 1992; Lake Tahoe, CA (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Council on Materials - DOE, Germantown; December 14-15, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - November 30 - December 4, 1992; Materials Research Society (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Spring 1993 - MRS - April 12-16, S.F. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Applied Physics Col. Committee (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Evetts Paper (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - GE Thermometers (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Cap and Gown Calendars, 82-83 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - White House, Remarks by the President, 8/18/87 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Bodega Bay Write-up (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Evaluations and Recommendations (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Paths to Higher Temperature Superconducters (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Preprints (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - RTS Workshop, Higher Temperature Superconductivity, Air Force documents (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Bodega Bay, Oct.1992 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Calendars: 1978-84, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - TECHNOLOGY: Concrete Technology Corp. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Letters (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Geballe - Refs., Correspondence 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1993: A-L (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Chron. 1993, TED: M-Z (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Chron. File 1991, TED: A-K (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Chron. File 1991, TED: L-Z (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - RECS 1993, TED (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations 1989: A-K (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Recommendations 1989: L-Z (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Project/Account Budget Expense Graphs: July - Nov., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Project/Account Budget Expense Graphs: Feb.- June, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Project/Account Budget Expense Graphs: July - Dec., 1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Project/Account Budget Expense Graphs: Dec. 1996 - June 1997 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Ref. Letters, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Applications and Attendee Lists (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Faxes Sent, Letters Rec’d, Addresses (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Gordon Research Conference (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations 1992: A-G (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Recommendations 1992: H-M (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations 1992: Mc.-Z (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Nate/Mark File 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Nate/Mark File 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Proposal Reviews, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Proposal Reviews, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Proposal Reviews, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Concise Encyclopedia of Magnetic and Superconducting Materials (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - ROHM and HAAS (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Advisee, Cohen, Uri (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Recommendations 1990: A-C (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Recommendations 1990: D-Mc (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations 1990: N-Z (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Misplaced Rec’s, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Rec. D. Yu (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Recommendations 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence 1990: A-G (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence 1990: H-Z (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 1989: A-G (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence 1989: H-R (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence 1989: S-Z (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence 1988: A-H (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence 1988: I-R (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 1988: S-Z (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence 1986: A-Z, A-F (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence 1986: G-N (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence 1986: O-Z (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - TED 1994: A-K (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - TED 1994: L-Z (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 1994 Chron. File Ted and Rec’s. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - TG Regret Letters (in alpha order) 1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2010-055
  - Correspondence A-D 1942-1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence E-G 1942-1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence H-K 1942-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence L-N 1942-1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence O-R 1942-1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence S-U 1942-1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence V-Z 1942-1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Index to correspondence Oct. 1952-May 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence 1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Jan.-May 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence June-Dec. 1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Jan.-Aug. 1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Sept.-Dec. 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence Jan.-May 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence June-Dec. 1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Jan.-April 1961 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence April-July 1961 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence Aug.-Dec. 1961 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence Jan.-Feb. 1962 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence March-May 1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Index to correspondence June 1962-Sept. 1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence May-June 1962 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence July-Aug. 1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Sept.-Dec. 1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence Jan. 1963 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence Feb.-April 1963 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence May-July 1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Aug.-Sept. 1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Index to correspondence Oct. 1963-Jan.1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Oct.-Dec. 1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Jan.-Feb. 1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence March-May 1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence June-Aug. 1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence Oct. 1964-Jan. 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Index to correspondence Feb. 1965-Jan. 1966 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence Feb.-April 1965 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence May-June 1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence July-Aug. 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence Sept.-Oct 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence Nov. 1965-Jan. 1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Index to correspondence Feb.-Dec. 1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence Feb. 1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence March 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence April-May 1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence June 1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence July-Sept. 1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence Oct.-Dec. 1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Index to correspondence Jan. 1967-Dec. 1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence Jan.-April 1967 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence May-June 1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence July-Oct. 1967 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence Nov.-Dec. 1967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (outgoing) A-J 1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (outgoing) K-Z 1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence A-E 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence F-J 1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence K-M 1968 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence N-R 1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence S-Z 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Index to correspondence 1968 (chronological) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (outgoing) Jan.-May 1968 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (outgoing) June-Dec. 1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (outgoing) Dec. 11 1968-March 1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (outgoing) April-Dec. 1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence A-C 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence D-F 1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence G-I 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence J-L 1969 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence M-O 1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence P-R 1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence S-T 1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence U-Z 1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence A-C 1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence D-F 1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence G-J 1970 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence K-M 1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence N-Q 1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence R-V 1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence W-Z 1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence A-C 1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence D-F 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence G-I 1971 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence J-M 1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence N-P 1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence Q-S 1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence T-V 1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence W-Z 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence A-B 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence C-D 1972 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence E-F 1972 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence G-I 1972 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence J-L 1972 (Box 6, Folder 12)